spicevod.com 2011-06-27

# Privacy | Spice Video On Demand

**SpiceVOD.com Spice Platinum Theater Privacy Policy**

AEBN, Inc. (?AEBN?) has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering practices for the SpiceVOD.com Spice Platinum Theater website located at www.SpiceVOD.com (the ?Site?).

Please note that this privacy policy applies solely to the Site, and does not apply to any other page on the websites located at www.SpiceTV.com (or any other website owned or operated by or on behalf of SpiceTV.com, Inc.) or on www.aebn.net. 

This site is owned and operated by: AEBN, Inc.  
AEBN, Inc.  
5300 Old Pineville Road Suite 160  
Charlotte, NC 28217  
Phone: 1.704.529.1600  
Customer Service Department: 1.800.628.0241  
mailto:mailto:billing@aebn.net 

**Cookies**

AEBN uses cookies on this Site to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our Site.

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on the Site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our Site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. For more information on cookies, click here.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site, but your ability to use some areas of our Site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our Site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Choice/Opt-out**

As an individual, you have the opportunity to limit the personal information you provide.

We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, our Site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (such as username and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user special offers and updates from AEBN. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the person when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings by logging into user info and un-checking the "would you like to receive special offers and updates from us?" checkbox. In addition, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at mailto:mailto:billing@aebn.net We offer an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications on our MY Account Section, or you may contact us at 704.529.1600, mailto:mailto:billing@aebn.net or 5300 Old Pineville Road Suite 160 Charlotte NC, 28217 to opt-out.

Except as already set forth in this privacy policy, you will be notified when any third party that is not our agent/service provider collects your personal information, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

**Information Collection & Use**

**Registration**

AEBN collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Site. For example, in order to use this Site, you must first complete the registration form and create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give contact information such as name and email address. We use this information to contact you about the services on our Site in which you have expressed interest.

You have the option to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender) to us; we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our Site.

Registered users may receive a newsletter or promotional materials from AEBN.

AEBN and SpiceTV.com, Inc. (?SpiceTV.com?) co-own the information collected on the SpiceVOD.com Site. Among other things, SpiceTV.com may use your personal information for marketing purposes, such as to provide information to you about SpiceTV.com, or about other companies in which SpiceTV.com believes you may be interested. Any use of your personal information by SpiceTV.com will be subject to the SpiceTV.com privacy policy located at http://tvclub.spicetv.com/legal/freelegal.html#privacypolicy.

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at mailto:mailto:billing@aebn.net by contacting us by telephone or postal using the information located at the top of this page.

**Downloadable Software**

AEBN provides Download Coach; a small software utility that makes your file downloading process a lot easier especially when files are very large. When you install this software, we do not include any Spyware adware. In addition, we do not collect any personal identifiable information during the program download or product registration. Please read the section below regarding AEBN?s use of non-personally identifiable information. 

**Surveys or Contests**

From time-to-time, we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our Site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor Site traffic or personalize the Site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys) and to send participants an email newsletter.

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company is prohibited from using our users' personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

**Tell-A-Friend**

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our Site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Site. AEBN stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at mailto:mailto:billing@aebn.net to request that we remove this information from our database.

**Email**

AEBN members and affiliates receive periodic email notices that include exclusive special offers, information about sales, promotions, new releases, and other relevant information. To unsubscribe from any list, click on the link at the top or bottom of the email you received and type your email address in the field marked "unsubscribe."

**Orders**

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

Our Site uses a secure online ordering system which enables clients to purchase minutes for viewing movies online, as well as rent movies. AEBN collects users? financial information; such as account and credit card numbers for verification purposes only. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services and never for any other reason.

**Non-personal information**

Like many Websites we collect and analyze standard log file information and Session ID information to analyze Site traffic, improve Site performance and to prevent fraud. Session IDs are bits of code on your computer that assist your browser in navigating our Site. We do not associate personal information with log file information or cookies, except when needed to prevent fraud.

**Affiliate and Webmaster sign-up**

AEBN collects prospective affiliate and webmaster contact information to process applications and conduct business. This information includes: name, checks payable, address, city, state/province, country, minimum payout, password, source of referral, tax ID (EIN or social security number for U.S. residents) and date of birth.

**Legal Disclaimer**

AEBN reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Site.

This Site contains links to other sites. AEBN is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. You should make sure that you read and understand the privacy policies of these sites and direct any concerns regarding external links to the site administrator or webmaster of that third party website.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, follow this link: Verisign.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Site, you can send email us at mailto:mailto:billing@aebn.net

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage and/or other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

The AEBN privacy statement was last updated on 12/14/2005.
